未来
The future.
一个黑暗 孤寂的世界
A dark, desolate world.
战争 苦难 死亡
A world of war, suffering, loss...
笼罩着双方
on both sides.
变种人和挺身而出帮助他们的人类
Mutants and the humans who dared to help them.
都在抵抗一个无法战胜的敌人
Fighting an enemy we cannot defeat.
这是我们不可避免的命运吗
Are we destined down this path?
和曾经无数种物种一样 走上自取灭亡的道路
Destined to destroy ourselves like so many species before us?
还是及时进化 以求改变自我
Or can we evolve fast enough to change ourselves?
改变命运
Change our fate?
未来是否真是定数
Is the future truly set?
它们来了
They're here!
来不及了
Time's up.
哨兵
Sentinels!
太阳黑子
Sunspot!
快走吧
Let's go.
快跑
Run!
快走
Go!
闪烁 不
Blink! No!
你来晚了 混蛋
Too late, assholes.
不许动 你这个变种人渣滓
Don't move, you mutant scum!
不
No!
趴在地上 双手放在头后面
Flat on the ground, hands behind your head!
我们的人所剩无几
So few of us left.
教授
Professor?
找到了
I've found them.
教授
Professor!
鲍比
嗨 暴风女
Bobby.
Hey, Storm.
嗨 小子
Hey, kid.
教授 你来了
Professor, you made it.
每次哨兵来袭 战戟都会发现它们
Whenever the Sentinels attack, Warpath spots them...
我送毕肖普回到袭击发生前
then I send Bishop back to warn us
去警告我们
of the attack before it happens.
让闪烁去找新的藏身处
Blink scouts the next site...
这样在它们找来之前我们就不在了
and then we leave before they ever know we were there.
因为 我们就没在过
Because... we never were.
什么叫你们就没在过
What do you mean you were never there?
她让毕肖普回到袭击发生的
She projects Bishop back in time
前几天去警告他们
a few days to warn the others...
未来的袭击
of the coming attack.
她能让毕肖普回到过去
So she sends Bishop back in time?
只是让他的意识回到他的过去
No, just his consciousness, into his younger self.
过去的身体里
His younger body.
喔
Wow.
这也许行得通 查尔斯
This might just work, Charles.
什么行得通
What might work?
哨兵计划最早是由玻利瓦尔·崔斯克博士提出的
The Sentinel program was originally conceived by Doctor Bolivar Trask.
他是70年代初期 世界顶尖的武器设计专家
In the early '70s, he was one of the world's leading weapons designers.
暗地里 他却在变种人身上进行着实验
But, covertly, he had begun experimenting on mutants...
利用他们的能力完成他的研究
using their gifts to fuel his own research.
这真是不可思议
This is extraordinary.
有一个变种人发现了他的研究内容
There was one mutant who had discovered what he was doing.
这家伙 可以随心所欲地变成 任何人
A mutant with the ability to transform herself into anyone.
魔形女
Mystique.
我认识的她叫瑞雯
I knew her as Raven.
我们从小相识
We met when we were children,
一起长大
grew up together.
她就像是我的妹妹
She was like a sister to me.
我想帮助她
I tried to help her...
没想到把她越推越远
but only succeeded in driving her away.
她走遍世界 追杀崔斯克
She hunted Trask across the world.
战争结束后 在1973年的巴黎会议上
And at the Paris Peace Accords in 1973,
越南战争后
after the Vietnam War...
她找到了崔斯克
she found Trask...
杀死了他
and killed him.
那是她第一次杀人
It was the first time she killed.
但不是最后一次
It wasn't her last.
崔斯克的死并没有导致她想要的结果
But killing Trask did not have the outcome she expected.
反而在一定程度上刺激了政府对
It only persuaded the government
哨兵计划的需求
of the need for his program.
他们当场抓住了她
They captured her that day...
折磨她 在她身上做实验
tortured her, experimented on her.
他们在她的DNA里发现了她具有变形能力的秘密
In her DNA, they discovered the secrets to her powers of transformation.
从此 他们就掌握了
It gave them the key they needed...
制造能应对任何变种能力的武器的关键所在
to create weapons that could adapt to any mutant power.
只用了不到50年
And in less than 50 years...
那种屠杀了我们众多同胞的
the machines that have destroyed...
机器就诞生了
so many of our kind were created.
一切都始于1973年的那一天
But it all started that day in 1973...
她第一次杀人那天
the day she first killed.
那天 她彻底变成了
The day she truly became...
魔形女
Mystique.
你想回到那一天
You want to go back there.
如果我能找到她 阻止她杀人
If I can get to her, stop the assassination...
不让她落入敌手
keep her out of their hands...
便能将哨兵计划扼杀在摇篮之中
then we can stop the Sentinels from ever being born.
让这场战争还没开始就结束
And end this war before it ever begins.
我可以送一个人回到几星期前
Uh, I can send someone back a couple weeks.
也许一个月前
Maybe a month.
可你要我送你回几十年前
But you're talking about going back decades.
教授 你拥有世界上最强的大脑
You have the most powerful brain in the world, Professor...
但是到了极限 它一样会崩溃
but the mind can only stretch so far before it snaps.
你会被撕成碎片 对不起
It would rip you apart. I'm sorry.
没人能承受这趟时空旅行
No one could survive that trip.
如果是一个大脑能自我修复的人呢
What if someone's mind has a way of snapping back?
一个即使被撕裂也能痊愈的人呢
What if someone can heal as fast as they're ripped apart?
这太冒险
It's a risk.
我知道
Yeah, I'm getting that.
不只是对你
Not just for you.
你这样 改变历史
You do this, you change history.
那是意义所在
Well, that's kind of the point.
我们中的某些人可能被杀
Some of us could be killed.
某些人可能永远不会出生
Some of us may never be born.
我们根本不能预料世界会产生什么改变
We have no idea how things may change.
我们还能继续坚持
We could keep going.
坚持反抗
Keep fighting.
直到何时
Until what?
你们得做出抉择
You've got a decision to make.
你们可以继续送毕肖普回到过去
You can keep sending Bishop back in time
反复地警告你们
over and over again to warn you,
直到某一天他失败了 你们也跟着丧生
until one day, he doesn't make it, and you all die.
或者你们放弃这次生命
Or you can give up this life.
那样他们和在这场战争中丧生的所有人
So that they and everyone else who died in this war
都能拥有未来
can actually have a future.
你是在要求我们把我们的生命牺牲给
You're asking us to sacrifice our lives
一个我们也许完全不曾存在的未来
for a future we might not even be a part of.
就是这样
Yes.
第二次机会
A second chance.
每个人的更好的机会
A better chance for everyone.
我的人手需要投票
My people need to vote.
他们刚刚投过了
They just did.
算上他们
They're in.
好了 大家散开
Okay, spread out.
各就各位
Take your positions.
我回到过去不知道在哪里的身体里
So I wake up in my younger body, God knows where.
然后呢
Then what?
你去我家找我 说服我
You'll need to go to my house and find me.
让我相信你说的那些事
Convince me of all of this.
你不能直接读心吗
Won't you be able to just read my mind?
1973年的我没有这种能力
I didn't have my powers in 1973.
罗根 我曾经为你做的事 现在你要为我做了
Logan, you're going to have to do for me what I once did for you.
指引我 引领我
Lead me, guide me.
那个与现在截然不同的我
I was a very different man then.
你要对我有耐心
You'll have to be patient with me.
我最擅长耐心了
Patience is my strongest suit.
你还要去找我
什么
You'll need me as well.
What?
魔形女离开查尔斯之后来找了我
After Mystique left Charles, she came with me...
是我使她走上了这条危险的路
and I set her on a dangerous path.
黑暗的路
A darker path.
你得让当年分道扬镳
It's going to take the two of us, side by side...
恩断义绝的我们携手合作
at a time when we couldn't be further apart.
好主意
Great.
我要去哪里找你
So where do I find you?
这有点复杂
Well, it's complicated.
你真的决定要这样做
Are you sure about this?
不只是他的能力受到考验
It's not just his power that'll be tested.
我知道这会对你造成什么影响
I've seen what this can do to you.
我能应对
I can handle this.
相信我
Trust me.
我猜我们要在来世相见了
I guess I'll see you in the next life.
当你的意识回到过去的时候
Basically, your body will go to sleep
身体就会陷入沉睡
while your mind travels back in time.
在这段时间 你的过去和现在是平行共存的
As long as you're back there, past and present will continue to coexist.
一旦你醒过来
But once you wake up...
你过去的作为就会覆盖历史
whatever you've done will take hold and become history.
而我们将只记得被改变后的历史
And for the rest of us, it will be the only history that we know.
过去的50年就将会不复存在
It will be like the last 50 years never happened.
这个时空 这场战争
And this world, and this war...
记得这一切的将只有你一个人
the only person who will remember it is you.
好了 罗根
All right, Logan...
现在你要清空思绪
I need you to clear your head
你要尽可能地保持平静
and to stay as calm as possible.
什么 什么意思
What? What do you mean?
如果你的意识过于波动 我会控制不住你
If your mind gets rocky, it will be harder for me to hold you...
你会掉进过去和未来的间隙里
and you could start to slip between past and future.
如果我有点小情绪呢
What if I need to get a little rocky?
想想平和的事
Think peaceful thoughts?
平和的事 有好消息吗
Peaceful thoughts... Do you have any good news?
喔 因为你不会变老 所以外貌不会改变
Well, you don't really age, so you'll pretty much look the same.
你能在过去停留的时间不多
You won't have much time in the past.
哨兵会找到我们
The Sentinels will find us.
每次都能
They always do.
这次我们将无路可逃
And this time, we won't be able to run.
只能坐以待毙
We'll have no escape.
这是最后的机会了
This is our last chance.
你确定这事能成
是啊 我相信他
You really think this will work?
I have faith in him.
我担心的不是他 是我们
It's not him I'm worried about, it's us.
年轻的我们
We were young...
还那么无知
we didn't know any better.
现在不会了
We will now.
回头见
See you all soon.
可能会有点疼
This might sting a little.
The first time
Ever I saw your face
喔
Whoa.
I thought the sun
Rose in your eyes
And the moon and the stars
Were the gifts you gave
我的天呐
Holy shit.
真回来了
It worked.
有事吗
Hey, what's going on?
格雯 快穿衣服
你们是谁
Gwen, get dressed.
Who the hell are you?
现在是什么情况
Hey, I don't know what's going on.
你的工作是
You're supposed to be
保护老板的女儿 而不是睡他
guarding the boss's daughter, not screwing her.
我没跟她睡
Well, I didn't sleep with her.
没有
No?
No.
我是说 对 我跟她睡了很多次
I mean, yes, I slept with her many times.
吉米
Jimmy!
不过那个人不是我 那是过去的我
That wasn't me. That was the old me.
我刚来到这里 还不到20秒
I just got here 20 seconds ago.
是吗
Really?
那你的衣服呢
Then what happened to your clothes?
我的 哦
My-- Oh.
如果说我是从未来来的
Would you believe me if I told you
你信吗
I was sent here from the future?
啊
Huh?
出去 亲爱的
好吧
Get out of here, sweetheart.
Yeah.
我们来解决这家伙
算了吧
We're gonna take care of this comedian.
No, you're not.
你是想把你的车钥匙和汽油钱给我
You're gonna give me the keys to your car and some money for gas...
还是想进医院
or you're gonna wake up in the hospital.
相信我 这事我见多了
Trust me, I know how these things play out.
因为你来自未来
Oh. Because you're from the future?
不
No.
是因为这玩意
Because of these.
什么情况
What the hell?
见鬼
God damn it!
想想平和的事
Peaceful thoughts.
吉米 雷蒙是怎么了
Jimmy! What happened to Ramon?
你为什么一直胡言乱语
And why are you talking crazy talk?
听着 嗯
格雯
Look, uh...
Gwen.
格雯 你将想低调行事几天 好吗
Gwen, you're gonna wanna lay low for a few days, all right?
从现在开始
Starting now.
好了 出去
Come on, out.
快走
Go.
嗯哼
Hmm.
今天 第18旅将从西贡撤离
Today, the 18th MP Brigade is departing from Saigon,
这是最后一支离开越南的美国军队
marking the last American troops to leave Vietnam.
显然战争结束了
and effectively ending the war.
国防支出正在接受重新审查
We are reviewing all of our defense expenditures...
所有灰色支出都将公布于众
and all the black books are being opened.
我们不会为威胁人民安全的武器提供资金
We can't support a weapon that targets our own citizens.
如果变种人像你说的
If these mutants, as you describe...
已经生活在我们当中
are already living among us...
这说明我们能够和平共处
then they are living here peacefully.
过去的10年我们一直相安无事
We haven't had an incident in over 10 years.
你忘了古巴的事了
After what happened in Cuba?
那件事从没被证实
That was never confirmed.
现在我们真正的敌人不是他们
We have very real enemies out there...
是俄国人和中国人
the Russians, the Chinese.
现在我们说的这些人在总人口中所占的
We are talking about a tenth of a tenth...
比例少之又少
of a tenth of our population.
请允许我念一份资料给各位听
Allow me to read something to you.
请吧
Please.
这份资料来自于中情局
This was acquired by our friends at the CIA.
是牛津大学一个变种人所
It's a dissertation...
撰写的论文
written by a mutant at Oxford University.
文章说
And I quote...
在尼安德特人眼里
"To Homo Neanderthalensis...
他的变种表亲 现代智人
"his mutant cousin, Homo Sapiens..."
也就是我们
which is us...
是一种畸形
"was an aberration.
变异人种现代智人出现后
"The arrival of the mutated human species, Homo Sapiens...
随之而来的是其低级同类 也就是尼安德特人的迅速灭亡
"was followed by the immediate extinction of their less evolved kin."
好了
Well...
现在 我们就是尼安德特人
Now, we are the Neanderthal.
只有你吧 崔斯克博士
Speak for yourself, Dr. Trask.
你们把士兵漂洋过海送上战场
You know, when you sent our soldiers to Vietnam...
却不给他们致胜武器
without the weapons they needed to win the war...
因为上一次你们低估了对手
you underestimated your enemy.
如果这次还这样
You do that with this enemy...
嗯
Mmm...
那就不是地球另一边的边境冲突了
and it won't be some border skirmish halfway around the world.
这次的战场 将是我们的街道
This time, the war will be for our streets...
城市 家
our cities, our homes...
到那时 你们才发现我研究的必要性
and by the time you see the need for my program...
那就已经晚了
it will be too late...
你们的人生将会留下两次战败的烙印
and you will have lost two wars in one lifetime.
对不起 崔斯克博士
We are sorry, Dr. Trask...
你的哨兵计划
but your Sentinel Program...
到此为止了
it ain't gonna fly.
有事吗 上校
Can I help you, Colonel?
我是来给我们的士兵送行的
Just here to give our boys a proper send-off.
抱歉 长官 按照命令 这是隔离区
I'm sorry, sir, but we have orders. This is a quarantined area.
让开 士兵
Stand aside, soldier.
这是命令
That's an order.
全体立正
Atten-hut!
稍息
At ease.
这些是什么
What is all this?
这是血液检测报告
Lab reports, blood tests.
之后会整理装箱运回去
It's all getting packed up and shipped back.
运到哪里
Where is it going?
到他们去的地方
Same place they are.
崔斯克集团
Trask Industries.
走了 先生们
Let's go, gentlemen.
我带你们离开这个倒霉地
I'm taking you out of this shit show.
是要回家吗
Shipping home?
还不到时候
Not just yet.
那是干什么用的
What are you doing with those?
让你们的旅途安稳点
Something to make the ride a little smoother.
你们会被送到一家私立机构
I'm transferring you to a private facility...
再做几项检查
where we can run a few more tests.
你们不是军人
Your men are not military.
是私人机构
Private outfit.
我们被授权送还他们
We're authorized to remand these men.
嗯
Hmm.
他们理应回家
These troops are going home.
哦 上校 恐怕你无权过问这件事
Well, Colonel, I don't believe you have jurisdiction in this matter.
恐怕我有 孩子
I'm afraid I do, son.
不好意思 你是谁
I'm sorry, who are you?
少校 你应该问
The question is, Major...
你是谁
...who are you?
瑞雯
Raven!
我不叫那名字
That's not my name.
我能解决
I had that.
我知道
I know.
我们撤 快 动作快
Let's move out. Come on, let's go.
埃瑞克呢
Where's Erik?
我现在单干了
I'm on my own now.
我们走 快点
Let's go! Move it!
让飞机等一下
Hold that plane!
不能把这些小伙子丢在这个无药可救的国家
Wouldn't wanna leave these boys in this godforsaken country.
是 长官
Yes, sir.
你不跟我们走吗
You're not coming with us, are you?
战斗还没结束
My war's not over.
敌人还没有消灭
The enemy is still out there.
那四个二等兵去哪里了
The four privates, where did they go?
去停机坪了
They were headed towards the tarmac.
有事吗
Can I help you?
这里的学校怎么了
Uh... Yeah, what happened to the school?
学校关了好几年了 你是家长吗
The school's been shut for years. Are you a parent?
最好别是 你是谁
I sure as hell hope not. Who are you?
汉克 汉克·麦考伊
I'm Hank. Hank McCoy.
我照看这房子
I look after the house now.
你是野兽
You're Beast?
难以置信 大器晚成啊
Look at you. I guess you're a late bloomer.
我听不懂你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about,
我得请你离开
but I'm gonna have to ask you to leave.
教授在哪里
So where's the Professor?
这里没有教授
There's no professor here.
瞧你瘦削的 还挺有力气
You're pretty strong for a scrawny kid.
你的体内真的没有小野兽
You sure there's not a little Beast in there?
他不在这里
得了吧 野兽
No, he's not here.
Come on, Beast.
得了吧 小野兽
不行
Come on, Beastie.
No.
嘿
Hey!
学校已经关门了
I said the school's closed.
请你离开
除非你让我见教授
You need to leave.
Not until I see the Professor.
我都跟你说了 这里没有教授
There's no professor here, I told you that.
孩子 我们以后会成为好朋友
Look, kid. You and I are gonna be good friends.
只是你还不知道
You just don't know it yet.
教授
Professor!
汉克
Hank?
怎么回事
What's going on here?
教授
Professor?
请别这么叫我
Please don't call me that.
为什么 你认识这家伙
Why? You know this guy?
他看起来似乎有点眼熟
Yeah, he looks slightly familiar.
快从吊灯上下来 汉克
Get off the bloody chandelier, Hank.
你能走路
You can walk.
你洞察力真强
You're a perceptive one.
我以为埃瑞克
I thought Erik--
奇怪的是
Which makes it slightly perplexing that
你竟然没看见大门口的警示牌
you missed our sign on the way in.
这里是私人领地 我的朋友
This is private property, my friend.
我要麻烦他请你离开这里
I'm gonna have to ask him to ask you to leave.
这个
Well.
恐怕办不到
I'm afraid I can't do that...
因为我是被派来找你的
because, uh, I was sent here for you.
那你回去告诉派你来的人我很忙
Tell whoever it was that sent you that I'm busy.
这事有点复杂
That's gonna be a little tricky...
因为派我来的人 就是你
because the person who sent me was you.
什么
What?
50年后的你
About 50 years from now.
我就知道 相信我
I know. Stay with me.
50年后的未来 是这样吗
对
Like in the future, 50 years from now?
Yeah.
我从未来派你来这里
对
I sent you from the future?
Yeah.
一派胡言
Piss off.
如果你没丧失能力 就知道是真的
If you had your powers, you'd know I was telling the truth.
你怎么知道我丧失能力
How do you know I don't have my p--
你是谁
我说了
Who are you?
I told you.
中情局的
不是
Are you CIA?
No.
你在监视我
You've been watching me?
我了解你 查尔斯
I know you, Charles.
我们是多年的朋友
We've been friends for years.
我知道你的能力始于9岁那年
I know your powers came when you were 9.
我知道 当你脑子里开始充斥各种声音时
I know you thought you were going crazy when it started...
你以为自己要疯了
all the voices in your head.
直到12岁那年
And it wasn't until you were 12...
你终于明白 这些声音来自于其他人的大脑
that you realized all the voices were in everyone else's head.
还要我说吗
Do you want me to go on?
我从没跟人说过
I never told anyone that.
现在没有 不过 以后会
Not yet, no, but, you will.
你勾起了我的好奇心
All right, you've piqued my interest.
你要干嘛
What do you want?
我们得阻止瑞雯
We have to stop Raven.
我需要你帮忙
I need your help.
我们需要你
We need your help.
如果是梦 我该醒了
I think I'd like to wake up now.
她跟这事有关系
What does she have to do with this?
你说
So you're saying...
他们窃取了瑞雯的能力 然后
they took Raven's power, and what?
使之武器化
They weaponized it?
对
Yep.
她很特别
She is unique.
是很特别 汉克
Yeah, she is, Hank.
起初 哨兵只是以变种人为目标
In the beginning, the Sentinels were just targeting mutants.
后来 它们开始识别普通人身上的变种基因
Then they began to identify the genetics in non-mutants...
那些可能会生出变种人后代的人
who would eventually have mutant children and grandchildren.
许多人类开始帮助我们 但世界还是落入了
Many of the humans tried to help us, but it was a slaughter.
最残酷无情的人手里
leaving only the worst of humanity in charge.
我经历过很多战争
I've been in a lot of wars.
从没见过这么惨烈的
I'd never seen anything like this.
这一切都是因为她
And it all starts with her.
就算我们退一万步说
Let's just say for the sake of...
再退一万步说 就算我相信你
the sake, that I choose to believe you...
我决定帮你 瑞雯也不会听我的
that I choose to help you. Raven won't listen to me.
她的心 和灵魂都在别人那里
Her heart and soul belong to someone else now.
我知道
I know.
所以我们也需要万磁王
That's why we're gonna need Magneto, too.
埃瑞克
Erik?
你知道他在哪里吗
对
You do know where he is?
Yeah.
能再说一遍吗
Could you give me that one more time, please?
你听到了
You heard me.
他在他该在的地方
He's where he belongs.
你打算就这么走了
You're just gonna walk out?
你的洞察力真的很强 我给你一百分
Ooh, top marks. Like I said, you are perceptive.
我认识的教授 绝不会丢下
The Professor I know would never turn his back...
走投无路的人
on someone who'd lost their path.
更不用说他爱的人
Especially someone he loved.
知道吗
You know...
我好像想起你了
I think I do remember you now.
对 高大暴躁发型矫情的家伙
Yeah. Tall, angry fellow with the contentious hair.
当年我们去找过你 求你帮忙
We came to you a long time ago... seeking your help.
你当时对我们说的话 我现在奉还
And I'm gonna say to you what you said to us then.
去你的
Fuck off.
听着 你这混蛋
Listen to me, you little shit.
我这一路走来 见过无数人死去
I've come a long way, and I've watched a lot of people die.
有好人 有朋友
Good people. Friends.
你再这么自暴自弃
If you're gonna wallow in self-pity...
无所作为 你也会见到这些
and do nothing, then you're gonna watch the same thing...
明白吗
you understand?
人都有一死
We all have to die sometime.
告诉过你 这里没有教授了
Told you there was no professor here.
他到底怎么了
What the hell happened to him?
他失去了一切
He lost everything.
埃瑞克 瑞雯
Erik, Raven...
和他的双腿
his legs.
我们建起学校 实验室 和这里的一切
We built the school, the labs, this whole place...
可是第一学期结束时
then, just after the first semester...
越南战场形势告急
the war in Vietnam got worse.
许多老师
Many of the teachers...
和学生被强征入伍
and older students were drafted.
他崩溃了
It broke him.
变得抑郁孤僻
He retreated into himself.
我想帮帮他
I wanted to help, do something...
所以我用帮我控制变身的配方
so I designed a serum to treat his spine...
发明了一种血清治疗他的脊椎
derived from the same formula that helps me control my mutation.
我只用少量 以保持身体稳定
I take just enough to keep myself balanced...
可他用得太多了
but he takes too much.
我想让他戒掉
I tried easing him back...
他忍受不了疼痛 和那些声音
but he just couldn't bear the pain, the voices.
治疗让他的腿能够继续使用
The treatment gives him his legs...
可这不够
but it's not enough.
他
He's...
他失去的太多了
He's just lost too much.
你不害怕我
You're not scared of me?
我一直相信这样的人不只我一个
I always believed I couldn't be the only one in the world.
我叫查尔斯·艾克斯维尔
Charles Xavier.
我叫瑞雯
Raven.
你饿了吧 就你一个人
You're hungry and alone.
你可以随便拿
Take whatever you want.
我们有很多食物 你不用偷
We've got lots of food. You don't have to steal.
其实
In fact...
你永远都不用再偷了
you never have to steal again.
真的 我向你保证
And that's a promise.
我帮你找她
I'll help you get her.
不是为了你的狗屁未来 我是为了她
Not for any of your future shite, but for her.
行啊
Fair enough.
可你并不了解埃瑞克
But I'll tell you this. You don't know Erik.
那家伙是怪物 是凶手
That man is a monster. A murderer.
你觉得你能说服瑞雯回心转意
You think you can convince Raven to change?
让她回家
To come home?
很好
That's splendid.
可是你为什么认为你能够改变埃瑞克呢
But what makes you think you can change him?
是你和埃瑞克一起派我来的
Because you and Erik sent me back here together.
他们用来关押他的房子
The room they're holding him in
建于二战期间
was built during the Second World War...
那时钢铁短缺
when there was a shortage of steel.
所以地基完全是由混凝土和沙土构成 不含金属
So the foundation is pure concrete and sand. No metal.
他被关在
He's being held...
这个星球上守备最森严的这座建筑物的
a hundred floors beneath the most
地下100层
heavily guarded building on the planet.
他怎么被关了
Why is he in there?
他没跟你说吗
What, he forgot to mention?
肯尼迪
Uh, JFK.
他杀了
He killed--
不然子弹怎么会奇迹般的在空中拐了个弯
What else explains a bullet miraculously curving through the air?
埃瑞克是操控枪支的高手
Erik's always had a way with guns.
你确定要这么做吗
Are you sure you want to carry on with this?
这是你的计划 不是我的
This is your plan, not mine.
我们目前还没有渠道能够进去
We don't have any resources to get us in.
或者出来
Or out.
我们没有帮手
It's just me and Hank.
我认识个人
I knew a guy.
他现在应该还很年轻
Yeah, he'd be a young man now.
在特区外长大
Grew up outside of D.C.
他能进入任何地方
He could get into anywhere.
可我不知道去哪里找他
I just don't know how the hell we're gonna find him.
主脑不在考虑范围内 是吧
Is Cerebro out of the question?
但愿你们有互联网就好了
If only you guys had Internet.
什么是互联网
What's "Internet?"
可以查电话
We have a phonebook.
我还以为您准备出差去了 先生
I thought you'd be getting ready for your trip, sir.
我回来取几份文件
I just came to grab a couple files.
新买的围巾 真漂亮
Is that a new scarf? It's nice.
谢谢
Thank you.
崔斯克博士
Dr. Trask?
请稍等
One second.
哦
Oh.
出席巴黎会议的人增加了
We added some names to the Paris meeting.
谢谢
Thank you.
出什么事了吗 先生
Is something wrong, sir?
没事 没事
No. It's nothing.
能麻烦你把我的行程打出来吗
Would you mind typing up my itinerary?
我不想忘了什么
I don't wanna miss anything.
这里 这里 这里
哪里
- Here, here, here.
- Where?
在这里停车
随便 都好
Just stop here.
All right, all right.
下次我来开 别习惯了
Next time I'm driving. Don't get used to it.
他又犯事了
What's he done now?
不管他拿了什么 我这就开支票
I will just write you a check for whatever he took.
我们只想跟他谈谈
We just need to talk to him.
彼得 是警察 他们又来了
Peter! The cops are here. Again.
我是公主 你是谁
I'm a princess. What are you?
我是金刚狼
I'm the Wolverine.
你的哥哥在哪里
Where's your brother?
上楼 烦你的姐姐去
Go upstairs and bug your sister.
是她在折磨我
But she bugs me!
你们想干嘛
What do you guys want?
我什么也没干 一直在这里
I didn't do anything. I've been here all day.
别紧张 彼得 我们不是警察
Just relax, Peter. We're not cops.
当然不是
Of course you're not. If you were,
警察怎么会开短租车
you wouldn't be driving a rental car.
你怎么会知道
How did you know we've got a rental car?
你进门的时候 我看了你的驾照
I checked your registration when you were walking to the door.
顺便
I also had some time to kill
看了你的租车合同
so I went through your rental agreement.
发现你们是从镇外来的 是FBI
Saw you were from out of town. Are you FBI?
不是警察 天才青少年学校是什么
No, you're not cops. Hey, what's with this gifted youngsters place?
那是 以前的名片
That's an old card.
他太神奇了
他太讨厌了
He's fascinating.
He's a pain in the arse.
是瞬移吗
What, a teleporter?
动作快而已
No, he's just fast.
我认识他时 他没这么 年轻
And when I knew him he wasn't so... young.
年轻 是你太老了
Young? You're just old.
你不害怕展示你的能力
So you're not afraid to show your powers?
能力 你说什么能力
What powers? What are you talking about?
有什么不正常的吗
Do you see something strange here?
就算说出去 也不会有人相信
Nothing anybody would believe if you told them.
你们是谁 想干嘛
So, who are you? What do you want?
想请你帮个忙 彼得
干什么
We need your help, Peter.
For what?
入侵一个高度戒备的地方
To break into a highly secured facility...
带一个人出来
and to get someone out.
劫狱
Prison break?
那可是犯法的
That's illegal, you know.
呃
Um...
除非他们抓到你
Well, only if you get caught.
我有什么好处
So, what's in it for me?
一个行窃惯犯 成功突破五角大楼
You, you kleptomaniac, get to break into the Pentagon.
凭什么相信你们
How do I know I can trust you?
因为我们是同类
Because we're just like you.
让他看看
Show him.
挺酷 就是有点恶心
That's cool, but it's disgusting.
五角大楼建于1943年 是世界最大的办公大楼
Built in 1943, the Pentagon is the world's largest office building...
超过25000名军方人员在此办公
housing more than 25,000 military employees...
占地600万平方英尺
stretched over six million square feet.
卫生间在哪里
Where's the bathroom?
他一直要方便
He always needs to pee!
监控都变成电视节目了 怎么回事
Yeah, we're getting broadcast signal down here. What's going on?
见鬼 打电话给维修部
Damn it, call Maintenance, get them down here.
从日本人手中夺取了硫磺岛
...fought for and captured the island of Iwo Jima from the Japanese Empire.
在这场历时一个月的战役中
Now, this month-long battle...
发生了二战太平洋战场
included some of the fiercest fighting
最激烈的战斗
during World War II in the Pacific...
再过3秒 这扇门就会打开
In three seconds, those doors are going to open...
会有20个警卫朝我们射击
and 20 guards will be here to shoot us.
我知道 等的就是这个
I know. That's what I'm waiting for.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
托住你的脖子 防止猛扭
I'm holding your neck so you don't get whiplash.
什么
What?
猛扭
Whiplash.
不许动
Don't move!
没事的 过会就好了
You're good, it'll pass.
大家都这样
It happens with everyone.
你犯的事一定不小
You must have done something pretty serious.
你干了什么
What did you do, man?
干了什么
What did you do?
干了什么 让他们兴师动众
What did you do? Why'd they have you in there?
刺杀了总统
For killing the President.
哇 啊
Ah. Wow. Shit.
我唯一的罪名
The only thing I'm guilty of
是为我们的同胞而战
is fighting for people like us.
会空手道吗 空手道知道吗
You take karate? You know karate, man?
我不知道什么是空手道
I don't know karate.
可我知道什么是疯子
But I know crazy.
女士们先生们 小伙们姑娘们 现在进入红色戒备状态
Ladies and gentlemen, boys and girls, this is a Code Red situation.
我和我的助手
We are evacuating the entire floor...
正在疏散整个楼层
so that my associate and I...
这样我们才能控制监狱的出口
can, uh, secure the prison.
你们是谁
Who are you?
我们是特别行动组 中央
We're special operations, CB...
联邦 情报调查局
FB-CID.
我刚才说的话 你们也许没听进去
Perhaps you didn't hear me when first I spoke...
可这事关重大
but it is imperative that you understand...
要知道这里现在已经被完全封锁了
we're in a complete lockdown situation.
你们现在得去三楼
We have to get you to the third floor--
不好意思 你说完了吗
Oh, I'm sorry. Were you finished?
他们说你能操纵金属
They told me you control metal.
他们
"They"?
知道吗 我妈以前认识个人 也能操纵金属
You know, my mom once knew a guy who could do that.
对不起 我这个人不是很提倡暴力
I'm sorry, I'm just not very good with violence.
查尔斯
Charles?
很高兴见到你 老朋友
Good to see you too, old friend.
你能走了
And walking.
与你无关
No thanks to you.
我今天最没预料见到的人就是你
You're the last person in the world I expected to see today.
相信我
Believe me...
不是迫不得已 我也不会来
I wouldn't be here if I didn't have to.
我救你出去 你就得听我的
If we get you out of here, we do it my way.
不许杀人
No killing.
没有头盔
No helmet.
我不想听你的也不行
I couldn't disobey you even if I wanted.
我再也不会进入你脑子了
I'm never getting inside of that head again.
我要你发誓 埃瑞克
I need your word, Erik.
都别动
Nobody move!
站在原地别动
Hold it right there!
查尔斯
不许动
Charles.
Don't move.
举起手来 不然我们就开枪了
Hands up, or we will shoot!
定住他们 查尔斯
我做不到
Freeze them, Charles.
I can't.
把手举起来
Hands up!
不
No!
If I could save time in a bottle
The first thing that I'd like to do
Is to save every day
Till eternity passes away
Just to spend them with you
If I could make days last forever
If words could make wishes come true
I'd save every day
Like a treasure and then
Again, I would spend them with you
But there never seems to be enough time
To do the things you want to do
Once you find them
I've looked around enough to know
That you're the one I want to go through time with
谢了 孩子
Thanks, kid.
彼得 真的非常感谢你
Peter, thank you very, very much.
多保重
You take care.
我看了座舱里的飞行计划
Hey, I saw your flight plan in the cockpit.
你们为什么要去巴黎
Why are you going to Paris?
如果你的爪子是金属的
Imagine if they were metal.
帮我把车还了
好的
Do me a favor and return it for me.
Okay.
彼得
And, Peter?
开慢点
Take it slow.
他们在哪里找到你的
Where did they dig you up?
你会觉得难以置信
You're gonna find this hard to believe...
是你派我来的
but, uh, you sent me.
你和查尔斯
You and Charles.
未来的你们
From the future.
怎么失去能力的
How did you lose them?
治疗脊椎的药物影响我的DNA
The treatment for my spine affects my DNA.
你为了走路 牺牲自己的能力
You sacrificed your powers so you could walk?
牺牲能力是为了睡个好觉
I sacrificed my powers so that I could sleep.
你懂什么
What do you know about it?
我也付出了很多代价
I've lost my fair share.
呵
Ha.
得了吧 埃瑞克
Dry your eyes, Erik.
这弥补不了你干过的事
It doesn't justify what you've done.
你根本不知道我干过什么
You have no idea what I've done.
我知道你夺走了我最重要的东西
I know that you took the things that mean the most to me.
也许你早该好好保护它们
Well, maybe you should have fought harder for them.
如果你想打架的话 埃瑞克
If you want a fight, Erik...
坐下
那我跟你打
- Sit down.
...I will give you a fight!
让他来
Let him come.
你抛下了我
You abandoned me!
夺走了她
You took her away...
还抛下了我
and you abandoned me!
萨尔瓦多天使
Angel.
红魔鬼
Azazel.
艾玛
Emma.
音波
Banshee.
变种人兄弟姐妹
Mutant brothers and sisters...
全都死了
all dead!
还有无数变种人
Countless others...
被实验
experimented on.
被杀戮
Butchered!
埃瑞克
Erik!
那时候你在哪里 查尔斯
Where were you, Charles?
我们应该好好保护他们
We were supposed to protect them!
你的同胞需要你的时候你在哪里
Where were you when your own people needed you?
躲起来了 你和汉克
Hiding! You and Hank!
把自己伪装起来了
Pretending to be something you're not!
埃瑞克
Erik!
你抛下了我们所有人
You abandoned us all.
原来你一直这么混蛋
So, you were always an asshole.
我猜我们在未来是好兄弟
I take it we're best buddies in the future.
很多年以来
I spent a lot of years
我一直想打倒你
trying to bring you down, bub.
结果怎么样
How does that work out for you?
你跟我一样
You're like me.
是幸存者
You're a survivor.
能收拾一下吗
Do you wanna pick all that shit up?
将军 你得少喝点 明天还有重要活动
我们在庆祝 队长 不是每天都能打赢战争 尤其是美国这个敌人
我去再拿一瓶
对不起
我相信是我的过失
你会说越南语
我是同声传译
会说许多语言
让我替你再买一瓶
除非有人陪你来的
就我自己
再来一瓶尊尼获加
你要出席明天的峰会
关心政治的美女
外表是会骗人的
女人
多展示点 宝贝
Show me more, baby?
衣服脱掉
Clothes off?
怎么了 宝贝 觉得我这样不美吗
What's the matter, baby? You don't think I look pretty like this?
下一盘吗 好久不下了
Fancy a game? It's been a while.
我没兴趣 谢谢
I'm not in the mood for games, thank you.
我已经10年没有碰过酒了
I haven't had a real sip in ten years.
总统不是我杀的
I didn't kill the President.
子弹变道了 埃瑞克
The bullet curved, Erik.
因为我想要救他
Because I was trying to save him.
可他们把我抓走了
They took me out before I could.
你为什么要救他
Why would you try and save him?
他是我们的一员
Because he was one of us.
你一定觉得我很蠢
You must think me so foolish.
你总说他们会找上门来
We've always said they would come after us.
我没想过他们会利用瑞雯的DNA
I never imagined they'd use Raven's DNA to do it.
你上次见她是什么时候
When did you last see her?
我去达拉斯那天
The day I left for Dallas.
她怎么样
And how was she?
坚强
Strong.
专注
Driven.
忠诚
Loyal.
她 她好吗
How... How was she?
她
She was...
我们
We were...
我理解你为什么这么看重她
I could see why she meant so much to you.
你该为她骄傲 查尔斯
You should be proud of her, Charles.
她在为我们的事业战斗
She's out there fighting for our cause.
是你的事业
Your cause.
我抚养长大的女孩不会杀人
The girl I raised was not capable of killing.
不是抚养 你们一起长大
You didn't raise her, you grew up with her.
她不可能永远是个小女孩 所以她走了
She couldn't stay a little girl forever, that's why she left.
她走 是因为你给她灌输了你的思想
She left because you got inside her head.
我没那种能力
That's not my power.
这是她的选择
She made a choice.
现在我们知道她选择的后果了
But now we know where that choice leads, don't we?
她去刺杀崔斯克
She's going to murder Trask,
被他们抓住
they're going to capture her...
然后他们把我们斩尽杀绝
and then they're going to wipe us out.
我们先找到她就能避免这些
Not if we get to her first.
只要明天我们改变历史
Not if we change history tomorrow.
对不起 查尔斯
I'm sorry, Charles...
以前的事情
for what happened.
真的很对不起
I truly am.
我好久没下棋了
It's been a while since I've played.
我会手下留情
I'll go easy on you.
那样对你公平一点
Might finally be a fair fight.
那你先下吧
You have the first move.
今天 来自世界各国的外交官
The diplomats from all around the world
陆续抵达皇家大酒店
are arriving here today at the Hotel Royal.
今天 将载入史册
It's an historic day.
美国政府正式宣布
It's the, uh, official ending
不再介入越南战争
of the United States' military involvement in Vietnam.
这是南越外交部部长
There we have the South Vietnamese Foreign Minister...
以及南越的其他政要
with other South Vietnamese dignitaries.
离峰会开始还有一个小时
The Summit doesn't begin for another hour.
我们在楼上为您的贵客
The hotel has arranged a private room
准备了一间专用房间
upstairs for your special guests.
时间足够了
That will be plenty of time.
下午好 诸位 感谢你们的到来
Good afternoon, everyone. Hello, thank you for coming.
祝贺你们赢得了这场战争
Congratulations on winning this war.
我知道 你们一会都要下楼
Now, I know you all have hands to shake
握握手 拍拍照
and photos to take downstairs...
所以 我就开门见山地说了
so I will get right to the point.
眼下出现了新的敌人
There is a new enemy out there.
在他们面前 你们的武器将失去作用
An enemy that will render your arsenals useless...
军队将失去力量
your armies powerless...
国家将失去自卫能力
and your nations defenseless.
要赢得这场战争 你们需要新武器 我将它们命名为哨兵
You will need a new weapon for this war. I call them Sentinels.
寓意是伫立在要塞大门外的
Named after the ancient guardians
古老守卫者
that stood at the gates of the citadel.
他们的飞行能力堪比鹞式战斗机
They have the aeronautic capabilities of a Harrier jet.
它们配备的枪械每分钟能发射
Armed with guns that can fire off...
超过2000发热塑性子弹
more than 2,000 rounds per minute of thermoceramic ammunition.
更别提它们的规模 力量 速度
But size, power, speed--
即便是洛克希德或波音也达不到
you could find that at Lockheed or Boeing.
不过 哨兵真正的特别之处
No, what makes the Sentinels so special...
在于它能够锁定变种人的基因
is the ability to target the mutant X-gene.
这套基因导航系统
A genetic guidance system
能在半英里外锁定目标
that can lock onto a mark a half a mile away.
只有在确定目标之后 才会发起攻击
It won't trigger unless it has identified the target.
有了这种武器
With this weapon, there will be
人员附带损失将成为历史
no human collateral damage.
就算我现在打开它 系统也不会启动
If I turn it on, the system couldn't even activate in here.
除非 这里有变种人
Unless there's a mutant.
它一定是出什么故障了
There has to be some kind of mistake.
我的发明从不出故障
My machines don't make mistakes.
你是什么
What are you?
我发誓我
I assure you...
不 别开枪
No, don't shoot it.
我发誓
I assure you,
我真的 不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
瑞雯
Raven!
瑞雯 瑞雯
Raven? Raven!
瑞雯
Raven?
查尔斯
Charles?
我们来找你了 我和埃瑞克一起
We've come for you, Erik and I.
来找你
Together.
我 我以为 再也 再也见不到你了
I never thought I'd see you again.
很久以前我保证过
I made you a promise a long time ago
我会保护你的
that I would protect you.
金刚狼
Wolverine!
我是绝对不会让他们抓到你的
I'm going to keep you safe.
I'm going to keep you out of their hands.
埃瑞克
Erik?
埃瑞克 你想干什么
Erik? What are you doing?
保护我们的未来
Securing our future.
原谅我 魔形女
Forgive me, Mystique.
只要你活着 我们就有危险
As long as you're out there, we'll never be safe.
埃瑞克
Erik...
用你的能力 查尔斯 阻止他
Use your power, Charles. Stop him.
他做不到
He can't.
他在脱离那个时空
He's slipping back.
我控制不住他
I'm losing him.
史崔克
Stryker!
总有人会完成我的事业 金刚狼
Someone will finish what we've started, Wolverine!
总有一天
One day!
控制住他
Restrain him.
埃瑞克
Erik!
这是哪里
Where am I?
啊
Huh?
我怎么跑到这里的
How the hell did I get here?
什么 是你找我们的
What? You came to us.
你是谁
查尔斯
Who are you?
Charles.
查尔斯·艾克斯维尔
Charles Xavier!
我不认识你
I don't know you.
啊
那是什么东西
Huh?
What the hell is that?
冷静 冷静 这里交给我 你快去
Whoa. Whoa. Look, I can deal with this. Just go.
阻止埃瑞克
Stop Erik!
埃瑞克 不要
Erik, please...
对不起
I'm sorry.
埃瑞克
Erik...
你是罗根 他是汉克·麦考伊 我是查尔斯·艾克斯维尔
You're Logan, that's Hank McCoy, I'm Charles Xavier.
这几天你一直跟我们在一起
You spent the last couple of days with us.
你服迷幻药了
You're on acid.
有人给你强效迷幻药了吧
Somebody gave you really bad acid, yeah?
冷静
Just hold on tight,
我们一起想办法
we'll get through this together.
天啊 凯蒂
Oh, my God, Kitty.
她伤得很重
She's wounded pretty bad.
我控制住他了
I got him.
教授
Professor?
你怎么了
What happened to you?
我见到了一个以后会让我
I just saw someone who's gonna
痛不欲生的人
bring me a lot of pain someday.
瑞雯哪里去了
Where's Raven?
跑了
什么
Gone.
What?
我们得走了
We have to get out of here.
我们想知道如果有关联的
We want to know if there's any sort of connection with--
昨天 一伙以前人们前所未见的不明歹徒
Yesterday, the Paris Peace Summit...
突然出现在巴黎会议现场
was rocked by the appearance of unidentified assailants...
全国上下陷入一片混乱
the likes of which the world has never seen.
大家都在问
Mass hysteria has gripped the nation as people ask...
他们来自哪里 他们还会再回来吗
"Where did they come from? Will they be back?"
最关键的问题是 他们是敌是友
And most importantly, "Are they friend or foe?"
以上是伦敦记者托比·艾略特
That was London correspondent Toby Elliot...
在巴黎会议现场为您带来的报道
reporting from the Paris Peace Summit yesterday.
愚蠢
Fuck me.
这到底是什么情况 别做记录
What the hell are we dealing with here? Off the record.
两天前 一个叫埃瑞克·兰谢尔的男子
Two days ago, this man, Erik Lehnsherr...
从五角大楼内最高警戒监狱逃脱
escaped from a maximum security prison inside the Pentagon.
我们认为这个女人
We believe that this woman
是兰谢尔过去的帮手
is a former associate of Lehnsherr's.
他们曾在1962年的
They were together in Cuba,
古巴导弹危机中出现过
day of the crisis in '62.
除此之外 兰谢尔还涉嫌刺杀肯尼迪总统
He was also implicated in Kennedy's assassination.
那么那个怪物呢
What about that thing?
我们不知道那是什么
We don't know what that thing is, sir.
确切地说 我们对他们一无所知
Actually, we really don't know what any of them are.
不 我们知道
Yes. Yes, we do.
他们是变种人
They're mutants.
这个男人能控制金属
He has the power to control metal.
如果我没记错
Last I checked, that's what
你们的武器都是金属做的
most of your weapons were made of.
而这个女人 则能变成任何一个人
And she can transform into anyone.
变成将军 特勤人员
A general, a secret serviceman.
甚至是 你 总统先生
Even you, Mr. President.
只要她想 她就能走进这间办公室
She could walk into this office...
下达一个核攻击命令
and order a nuclear strike if she was in the mood.
而他们只是冰山一角
And that's only two of them.
那我们有什么对策 或者防御手段
Do we have any countermeasures? Any defense?
我就等你问这个问题
I was waiting for you to ask me that question.
他的项目还在实验阶段 而且严重违规
That's an experimental program, sir. Strictly off the books.
你是不是想告诉我 对于这些变种人
You're telling me these mutants are out in the world...
我们最好的防御手段 是金属机器人
and our best defense are these giant metal robots?
很多变种人与我们外形相似
Many of the mutants look like us.
但我的哨兵能分辨出来
My Sentinels can tell the difference.
我有8架样机可以使用
I have eight prototypes ready to go.
它们都由划时代的聚合物制成
They're built out of a space-age polymer,
不含一点金属成分
not an ounce of metal on them.
那就办个展示会
I want to make a demonstration.
我要让世界知道 我们有能力保护大家
I want the world to know that we can protect them.
实施这个项目要多少钱
What do you need to get these things operational?
我向议会申请过资金
I already gave that number to Congress.
很可惜被他们投票否决了
Unfortunately, they elected to shut me down.
要让它们动起来 只需要花一点小钱
It's going to cost a bit more to turn them on.
尽管开口
噢 还有一件事情
- Whatever you need.
- Oh, and one more thing.
如果能够抓到他们的话 我非常需要她
If we do manage to capture them, I would like her.
当然 出于研究目的
For research purposes, of course.
我不在乎你糟蹋谁 不是我就行
I don't care who you screw, as long as it's not me.
真可怕
什么真可怕
生来就是那副幅模样
可怕吗
你能想象
每次照镜子都能看到它看着你的感觉吗
是的 我能
你觉得她是从哪里来的
你觉得她有家人吗
是的
Yes.
她有
She does.
只要让我看见一颗螺丝动了
If I see so much as a screw move,
我就把它插进你的脖子
I will jam this into your throat.
你怎么找到我的
How did you find me?
你教导有方
You taught me well.
很久没这么亲密交流了
It's been a long time since we were this close.
我想你
I missed you.
你想杀我
You tried to kill me.
这样其他变种人才能活
So the rest of us could live.
什么意思
What do you mean?
我们收到了来自未来的消息
We received a message from the future.
你别想骗我
Don't lie to me.
我从没骗过你 以后也不会
I never have, and I never will.
人类会利用你的血液和基因
Humans use your blood, your genes,
制造出武器 将我们斩尽杀绝
to create a weapon that wipes us all out.
我只是做了为保护我们的
I was only doing what I thought
未来而必须做的事情
necessary to secure our future.
你有什么理由能让我不
So what's to stop me from killing you
割断你的喉咙保护我的未来
right now and securing my future?
没有
Nothing.
已经无所谓了
It doesn't matter anymore.
他们有你的DNA 你的血滴在马路上
They have your DNA. Your blood was on the street.
这些都怪谁
Whose fault was that?
怪我
Mine.
我见过他们的计划 武器制造早就开始了
I've seen their plans. They're creating a weapon.
现在他们得到了更进一步的关键
And now they have what they need to take it further.
我们必须先发制人 趁我们还处在上风
We have to strike now, while we still hold the upper hand.
我看到太多朋友死了 埃瑞克
I've seen too many friends die, Erik.
我不想发动战争
I don't want a war.
我只想要凶手偿命
I only want the man who murdered them.
这就是战争
This is war.
你怎么了
What happened to you?
我不在的时候 你丧失自我了
Did you lose your way while I was gone?
你是查尔斯的瑞雯
Are you still Charles' Raven?
还是魔形女
Or are you Mystique?
崔斯克才是敌人
Trask is the enemy.
杀了他一个还不够
Killing one man isn't enough.
对你来说永远不够
It never was for you.
再见 埃瑞克
Goodbye, Erik.
他怎么了
What happened?
过来
还能走吗
Come on.
Can he walk?
他需要治疗
He needs his treatment.
汉克 我能听见他们
Hank, I can hear them.
我知道 没事的
I know. It's okay.
能让声音停下吗
我这就去拿
Can you make it stop?
I'll get them.
嘿 嘿
Hey, hey.
振作一点
Pull yourself together.
末日还没到呢
It's not over yet.
这话你自己都不信
You don't believe that.
你怎么知道
How do you know?
这里不行了
As these go...
这里就恢复了
this comes back.
全部都回来了
They all come back.
听着
Look.
我还在这里
I'm still here...
瑞雯还不知去向
and she's still out there.
我们需要你帮忙 查尔斯
We need your help, Charles.
真正的你
Not like this. I need you.
没有你的能力 我们找不到瑞雯
We can't find Raven. Not without your powers.
你少打了一次 所以我增加了剂量
I added a little extra because you missed a dose.
查尔斯
Charles.
汉克 帮我个忙好吗
Hank, do me a favor.
扶我到书房去 好吗
Would you help me to my study, please?
来吧
Come on, I got you.
你确定要这么做
Are you sure about this?
不能确定
Absolutely not.
这真是不可思议
This creature is extraordinary.
她的基因中也许能找到
Her genes could hold the key
变种的关键
to mutation itself.
还有吗
I need more.
从巴黎的街头刮下来的就这么多了
That's all they were able to scrape off the pavement in Paris.
不只是血
More than blood.
我需要脑组织
I need brain tissue...
脊髓液 骨髓
spinal fluid, bone marrow.
想象一下
Imagine...
哨兵能够根据目标进行
Sentinels that could transform,
任意变形
adapt to any target.
只要我能够抓到她
If I could just get my hands on her.
这姑娘能够让项目进度
This girl could leap
加快几年
the program forward years...
甚至几十年
decades into the future.
你儿子几岁 少校
How old is your son now, Major?
杰森
Jason?
就快10岁了 长得真快
He's coming up on ten now, if you can believe it.
再过8年就是入伍的年龄了
Eight years from fighting age.
有多少人的儿子和兄弟
And how many of our sons and brothers
是被装在尸体袋里运回来的
did we just ship home in body bags?
是50000 还是55000
Maybe fifty, fifty-five thousand?
还有我们的敌人呢
And how many more on the other side?
在这之前
Never before...
我们人类的历史上
in all of human history...
还从来没有任何事情 能把全人类都团结在一起
has there been a cause which could unite us as a species.
现在有了
Until now.
你还真是痛恨变种人
You really hate, mutants, don't you?
恰恰相反 我很欣赏他们
On the contrary, I rather admire them.
欣赏他们的能力
The things they can do.
我把他们视为人类的救星
I see mutants as our salvation.
也是人类的敌人
A common enemy.
我们共同战斗 抵抗终极的敌人
A common struggle against the ultimate enemy.
灭绝
Extinction.
我相信我们的新朋友
I believe our new friends...
将帮助我们进入一个新纪元 比尔
are going to help us usher in a new era, Bill.
一个真正的
A new era of genuine...
持久的 和平的新纪元
and long-lasting peace.
注意 注意
Attention, attention.
运输车将在两个小时后出发
Transport departure in two hours.
重复 运输车将在两个小时后出发
Repeat. Transport departure in two hours.
你上次下来是什么时候
When was the last time you were down here?
上次下来找学生的时候
The last time we went looking for students.
像是上辈子
A lifetime ago.
欢迎 教授
Welcome, Professor.
瑞雯受伤了 应该走不远
Raven's wounded. She won't be moving fast.
我已经很久没活动过这套筋骨了
These are muscles I haven't stretched in a long time.
查尔斯
Charles!
查尔斯 你还好吗 没事吧
Charles? It's all right.
我去检查一下发电机
I'll go check the generator.
不是设备问题 对吗
It's not the machinery, is it?
我做不到 我的脑子
I can't do this. My mind...
你能做到
Yes, you can.
我承受不了
你只是有些生疏
It won't take it.
You're just a little rusty.
你不明白 不是生疏的问题
You don't understand. It's not a question of being rusty.
我能打开开关 我能扭动旋钮
I can flip the switches. I can turn the knobs.
但我的力量来自这里 这里
But my power comes from here. It comes from--
这里坏了
And it's broken.
我就像我的学生一样
I feel like one of my students.
很无助
Helpless.
下来就是个错误
It was a mistake coming down here.
放埃瑞克出来就是个错误
It was a mistake freeing Erik.
这整件事就是个大错误
This whole thing has been one bloody mistake.
对不起 罗根 他们不该派你回来
I'm sorry, Logan, but they sent back the wrong man.
说得对
You're right.
不该是我
I am.
本该是你来的
Actually, it was supposed to be you.
可只有我的身体能承受这趟旅行
But I was the only one who could physically make the trip.
我也
And, uh...
不知道还能待多久
And I don't know how long I've got here.
可我知道 很久以前
But I do know that a long time ago...
正确地说 是很久以后
actually, a long time from now...
我曾是你最无助的学生
I was your most helpless student.
是你 解开了我的心结
And you unlocked my mind.
是你 告诉我我是谁
You showed me what I was.
我能成为什么
You showed me what I could be.
我不知道应该怎么帮助你
I don't know how to do that for you.
你说得对 我不知道
You're right. I don't.
但是有人知道
But I know someone who might.
嗯哼
Hmm.
进入我的大脑
Look into my mind.
你看到我用主脑的后果了
You saw what I did to Cerebro.
你不想跟它一样吧
You don't want me inside your head.
你什么都不做
There's no damage you can do...
是伤害不了我的 放心吧
that hasn't already been done. Trust me.
来吧
Come on.
嗨
Hey.
嗨 罗根
Hey, Logan.
嗨 琴
Hi, Jean.
杀了我
Kill me.
我爱你
I love you.
你这个可怜的人
You poor, poor man.
跳过我的
Look past me.
我不想要你的痛苦
No, I don't want your suffering.
我不想要你的未来
I don't want your future!
跳过我的未来
Look past my future.
看你的未来
Look for your future.
很好
That's it.
就这样
继续
That's it.
查尔斯
Charles.
这就是我们的结局
So this is what becomes of us.
埃瑞克说得对
Erik was right.
是我们心太软的下场
Humanity does this to us.
除非我们能展现一个不同的未来
Not if we show them a better path.
你还不放弃
You still believe?
人偶尔一次失足 迷失了方向
Just because someone stumbles, loses their way...
不等于永远会迷失下去
it doesn't mean they're lost forever.
有时候 我们只需要有人搭把手
Sometimes we all need a little help.
我不是从前的我了
Oh, I'm not the man I was.
我一使用能力
I open my mind...
它就会把我彻底压垮
and it almost overwhelms me.
你在害怕 主脑能够感觉到
You're afraid, and Cerebro knows it.
那些声音实在是
All those voices...
实在是太痛苦了
so much pain.
你害怕的不是别人的痛苦
It's not their pain you're afraid of.
是你自己的
It's yours, Charles.
痛苦虽然可怕
And as frightening as it may be...
却能够让你变得强大
that pain will make you stronger.
如果你能让自己感受它
If you allow yourself to feel it...
接受它
embrace it...
它将会让你变得
it will make you more powerful
超乎想象的强大
than you ever imagined.
我们拥有的
It's the greatest
最强大的能力
gift we have...
是坚强地承受
to bear their pain
他人的痛苦
without breaking.
而这种能力来自
And it's born...
最具人性的力量
from the most human power.
希望
Hope.
拜托 查尔斯
Please, Charles...
我们需要你重拾希望
we need you to hope again.
找到你想要的了吗
Find what you were looking for?
电力恢复了
The power's back on.
是的
Yes.
是恢复了
Yes, it is.
她失血过多
She's lost too much blood.
不能再继续下去了
She can't keep going like this.
我们别无选择 鲍比
We have no choice, Bobby.
叫醒他就行了
不行
We can wake him up.
No!
他们还需要时间
They need more time.
我刚才
I had...
看见了过去
a glimpse into the past.
如果我们现在叫醒他
If we wake Logan now...
我们的命运将会走向更加黑暗的结局
we may set our fate on an even darker course.
他们还需要时间
They need more time.
还有一个变种人可以
There is someone else.
不 没有变种人有凯蒂的能力
No, no one has Kitty's power.
有一个能吸收她的能力的变种人
Someone that could take her power,
可以接替她
take her place.
她吸收过你的能力
She took yours once.
小淘气
Rogue.
我很抱歉 鲍比 她已经死了
I'm sorry, Bobby, she must be dead.
我已经很多年
I haven't been able to make
没有联系到她了
a connection with her for years.
那是因为他们把她关押在
That's because they're keeping her
你的大脑无法进入的
in the one place your mind can't reach
一个地方
from the outside.
她在主脑
She's in Cerebro.
她在你的家 教授
She's in your house, Professor.
他们在用她做实验
They're experimenting on her.
试图汲取她的能力 来夺取我们的能力
Trying to tap into her power, so they can take ours.
夺取所有变种人的能力
Take all of ours.
如果你知道她活着 为什么不去救她
If you knew this, why didn't you go after her?
我们试过 但戒备森严
We tried. It's too heavily guarded.
我知道一些他们不知道的
I may know a few things
我的家的事
about that house they don't.
凯蒂 我要去帮忙了
Kitty, I'm going to get help.
我要带一个人回来帮你
I'm gonna bring back somebody to help you.
把你自己带回来就好
Please, just bring yourself back.
瑞雯 好了
Raven, stop.
别再逃避了
Stop running.
查尔斯
Charles?
你在哪里
Where are you?
我在家里
Back at the house...
你该待的地方
where you should be.
你该回家了
I need you to come home.
我知道自己该干什么
I know what I need to do.
如果你杀了崔斯克
If you kill Trask...
会出现更多跟他一样的人
you will be creating countless more just like him.
那就把他们都杀了
Then I'll kill them, too.
这是埃瑞克的思想 不是你的
Those are Erik's words, not yours.
哦
Oh!
和我一起长大的那个女孩不会杀人
The girl I grew up with wasn't capable of killing.
她善良
She was good...
公正 富有同情心
fair, full of compassion.
我有同情心
I have compassion.
但不是给崔斯克
Just not for Trask.
他杀了我们太多同胞
He's murdered too many of us.
直接放倒她 查尔斯 进入她的大脑
Shut her down, Charles. Get in her head.
她不让我进去
She's not letting me in.
我只能保持联系 我还不够强大
I'm barely holding on. I'm not strong enough yet.
我知道崔斯克的恶行
I know what Trask has done...
可杀了他 死去的人也回不来
but killing him will not bring them back.
杀了他 只会把你送上
It will set you on a path...
一条不归路
from which there is no return.
永无止境的杀戮
An endless cycle of killing.
彼此残杀 直到灰飞烟灭
Us and them, until there is nothing left.
你和我 我们能阻止这一切
But we can stop it, right now, you and I.
你必须要回家
You just have to come home.
必须要
I have to?
你还是老样子 查尔斯
You haven't changed at all, Charles.
我说了
Like I said...
我知道自己该干什么
I know exactly what I have to do.
你知道
You do?
那么 无论你去哪里 我都会找到你
Then, wherever you go, I will find you.
瑞雯 如果你逼迫我 我会阻止你
And, Raven, if you make me, I will stop you.
好运 查尔斯
Good luck, Charles.
她在哪里
Where is she?
她在机场 准备登机
She's in an airport, boarding a plane.
她可以去任何地方
She could be going anywhere.
休息吧 查尔斯
Get some rest, Charles.
我们会在早上追踪她查出
We'll track her in the morning and find out
她要去哪里
exactly where she's going.
火箭确实在基地外坠毁
...rockets did land outside the base,
5死12伤
killing five civilians and wounding 12 others.
在
Yeah?
你知道那玩意含有致癌物吧
You know that those things can give you cancer?
我在实验室做过毒品测试
I've done some toxicology tests in the lab, and...
你是想知道什么吧
You want something?
对 我来
Yeah, I'm...
我知道这很复杂
I know it's complicated,
可能有各种你能说
and there's probably all kinds of rules
不能说的规则和原因
and reasons for what you can and can't say,
但我想你你能不能告诉我
but I was wondering if you could tell me
在未来 我活着吗
in the future, do I make it?
没有
No.
哦
Oh.
好吧
Okay.
没关系 一样感谢
It's okay. Thanks.
嘿 小子
Hey, kid?
我就是来自那个世界
It's just the world I came from.
我们要回到过去
We're going backwards in time.
明天 我们的总统
Tomorrow, in front of the White House,
将在白宫发表声明
the President will make his announcement.
出席的还有国防部长莱尔德
He will be joined by Secretary of Defense Laird...
以及处理变种人问题上
and has even sought the help
提供特别指导帮助的
of renowned scientist Bolivar Trask...
著名科学家玻利瓦尔·崔斯克
his special advisor to combat this mutant issue.
白宫已经要求三大电视网
The White House has asked all three networks
直播这一活动
to air the event live,
这不仅对美国
as it is a matter of importance
至关重要
not only to the United States,
对全球每个公民也是
but to every citizen from around the globe.
这个活动尚无其它动向
There are no other details about the event...
瑞雯
Raven...
我的天
My God.
我不明白 你在这里做什么
I don't understand. What are you doing here?
我
I, uh...
我猜 我只是意识到
I guess, I just realized
我无处可去了
I have nowhere else to go.
我去叫醒查尔斯
不 不要
I've gotta wake Charles...
No, don't.
先等等
Just wait.
你真不该走上这条路的
You really shouldn't walk on this.
我经历过更糟的
I've had worse.
你这几年一直住在这里
So, you've been living here all these years?
总得有人照顾查尔斯
Someone had to take care of Charles.
你知道的 他想念你
You know, he's missed you.
他想念曾经的我
He misses who I was.
我不是他希望的样子了
I'm not who he wants me to be anymore.
我想念你
I've missed you.
你现在一直这副模样了
So, you're like this all the time now.
什么模样
Like what?
这样
This.
不是一直这副模样
No, not all the time.
我早上注射一次
I take a shot in the morning,
激动时再注射一次
and I need another if I get worked up.
激动
Worked up?
对 对 感觉情绪强烈
Yeah, yeah,when I'm...
或兴奋的时候
...emotional or excited.
任何动物都会
Any animal urges.
嗯
Hmm.
通常 我能摆脱它们
Usually, I can fight them off.
也许 我们不该摆脱
Well, maybe, we shouldn't have to fight off
我们的天性
the things that come naturally to us.
你记得最后你对我说了什么吗
Do you remember one of the last things you said to me?
我这副模样 永远不会被认为是美丽
That I would never be deemed beautiful, looking like this?
你还这么想吗
Do you still think that?
也许吧 你看到巴黎发生了什么
Maybe. You saw what happened in Paris.
你知道他们怎么看待我们
You know what they think of us.
你怎么想
What do you think?
我认为你很美丽
I think you're beautiful.
你自己呢
What about yourself?
你该休息了
You should get some rest.
你回家我很高兴
I'm glad you're home.
汉克
Hank?
你记得最后我对你说了什么吗
Do you remember the last thing I said to you?
是 变种人和自豪
It was, "Mutant and proud."
旧天然气管道和水管直朝房子
The old gas and water pipes lead straight to the house.
墙是强化钢筑成的
The walls are made of reinforced steel.
也就是 一扇门
In other words, a door.
你们现在直接走过大厅
You're walking directly over the hall now.
曾经我也趟在那块平板上
I've been on that slab.
我告诉你们那是什么感受
Let me show you how it feels.
小淘气 小淘气 快 醒醒
Rogue, Rogue, come on. Wake up.
小淘气
Rogue.
快 小淘气 醒醒 醒醒 是我
Come on, Rogue, wake up. Wake up, it's me.
不
No.
小淘气 小淘气 小淘气 没事的 我们一起来的
Rogue, Rogue, Rogue, it's okay. He's with me.
来救你出去
We're gonna get you out of here.
埃瑞克 鲍比
Erik, Bobby.
逃出去 快逃
Get out of there! Now!
带她走
Take her!
鲍比 不要
Bobby! No!
鲍比
Bobby!
教授
Professor!
快离开这里
Get us out of here.
鲍比
我知道
Bobby.
I know.
我很抱歉 查尔斯
I'm sorry, Charles.
鲍比呢
Where's Bobby?
我很遗憾 凯蒂
I'm sorry, Kitty.
你好 罗根
Hello, Logan.
小淘气
Rogue.
瑞雯来过了
Raven was here.
我搞砸了
糟了
I screwed up.
Shit.
我们现在没法追踪她了
We can't track her now.
她切断了纽带
She's cut her ties.
我昨晚听新闻报道
Hey, I saw in the news last night
下午在华盛顿有一个
there's going to be an announcement in Washington this afternoon
关于变种人的新草案的通告
about a new protocol for mutants.
我发明了这套系统
I set the system I designed...
录制三大电视网报道巴黎的新闻
to record any news about Paris over all three networks...
还有公视网
and PBS.
三大电视网 喔
All three? Wow.
对 还有公视网
Yeah, and PBS.
看我找到了什么
Look what I found.
明天 我们的总统
Tomorrow, in front of the White House,
将在白宫发表声明
the President will make his announcement.
出席的还有国防部长莱尔德
He will be joined by Secretary of Defense Laird...
以及处理变种人问题上
and has even sought the help
提供特别指导帮助的
of renowned scientist Bolivar Trask...
著名科学家玻利瓦尔·崔斯克
his special advisor to combat this mutant issue.
白宫已经要求
The White House has asked--
瑞雯不明白
Raven doesn't realize...
如果她在这样一个受全世界瞩目的活动上
that if she kills Trask at an event like that...
杀了崔斯克
with the whole world watching...
那样的话 我就白来了
Then I came a long way for nothing.
还有更糟的 有报道说
And there's more bad news. I saw in a report...
他们在巴黎拿到了她的血液样本
they found traces of her blood in Paris.
说不定 他们已经得到了她的DNA
For all we know, they already have her DNA...
万事俱备
which is all they'd need.
就差制造未来哨兵了
To create the Sentinels of the future.
量子论里有一种理论
There's a theory in quantum physics...
时间是永恒的
that time is immutable.
就像河流 扔快石头
It's like a river. You can throw a pebble into it...
会有波浪 但最终会恢复平静
and create a ripple, but the current always corrects itself.
无论你做什么 河还是朝同样的方向流去
No matter what you do, the river just keeps flowing in the same direction.
你想说什么
What are you trying to say?
我想说
What I'm saying is...
如果战争不可避免
what if the war is inevitable?
如果她注定要杀死崔斯克
What if she's meant to kill Trask?
或许她就是这样的人
What if this is just simply who she is?
人偶尔一次失足
Just because someone stumbles,
迷失了方向
loses their way...
不等于永远会迷失下去
doesn't mean they're lost forever.
我不相信那套理论 汉克
No, I don't believe that theory, Hank.
我不相信她是那样的人
And I cannot believe that is who she is.
准备飞机
Ready the plane.
我们去华盛顿
We're going to Washington.
你没事吧
You all right?
好多了
Getting there.
无论发生什么 你都要答应我一件事
Whatever happens today, I need you to promise me something.
你在我的大脑里看见了许多悲伤回忆
You've looked into my mind and seen a lot of bad...
可也有美好回忆
but you've seen the good, too.
X战警
The X-Men.
答应我 你会找到我们
Promise me you'll find us.
用你的力量 把我们聚在一起
Use your power, bring us together.
指引我们 引领我们
Guide us. Lead us.
暴风女 斯科特
Storm. Scott.
琴
Jean.
记住这些名字
Remember those names.
我们有很多人
There are so many of us.
我们需要你 教授
We will need you, Professor.
我会尽力的
I'll do my best.
这就足够了
Your best is enough.
相信我
Trust me.
发现12架运输机 10英里外
There's 12 carriers inbound, 10 miles!
它们找来了
They've found us.
今天将有数千人聚集于此
of people will be gathered here today.
他们从世界各地赶来
They've come from all over the world...
与至少50个国家的新闻工作者
to witness history, along with news crews...
一起见证历史
from at least 50 different countries.
谢谢
Thank you.
能看一下邀请函吗
Can I see your invitations, please?
当然可以
Yes, you may.
这两个人跟我一起的
These two are with me.
进去吧
Go ahead.
谢谢
Thank you.
罗根
Logan!
请这边走 先生
Please, this way, sir.
第4步兵师 遭遇了德国s型地雷
Fourth infantry... Took a Bouncing Betty.
你遭遇了什么
What happened to you?
己方误伤
Friendly fire.
最糟的那种
The worst kind.
对
Yeah.
我还没找到她 但她一定在这里
I haven't found her yet, but she has to be here.
有请总统先生
The President of the United States.
各位同胞们
My fellow Americans...
今天 我们面临着有史以来最严峻的威胁
today we face the gravest threat in our history...
变种人
mutants.
我们已经做好了准备
We have prepared for this threat.
借用罗伯特·奥本海默的名言
In the immortal words of Robert Oppenheimer...
看啊
"Behold.
世界将从此彻底改变
"The world will never be the same again."
要帮忙吗
Can I help you?
不需要
No, you can't.
它们来了
Here they come.
为了变种人兄弟姐妹
This is for you, brothers and sisters.
瑞雯
Raven?
找到她了
I have her.
让我去 查尔斯
Let me go, Charles.
在那里 看见了吗
There. You see?
那个特勤人员
Secret Serviceman.
在舞台左边
Left of the stage.
看到了
快去
Got him.
Go.
你在闹什么
What the hell are you doing?
我没让你启动它们
I didn't tell you to activate them.
我没有
I didn't.
瑞雯 求你听我说
Raven, please, listen to me.
上天给了我们第二次机会 让世界重新认识我们
We've been given a second chance to define who we are.
别这么做
Don't do this.
先生们 你们不能过去
Gentlemen, you cannot pass this point.
我们阻止不了那么多
We can't stop that many.
对 但我们能拖住它们
No, but we can slow them down.
埃瑞克
Erik!
啊
Ah!
暴风女
Storm!
快点 跟上 我们走
Go, go, go!
小心碰头
Watch your head!
快 快 快
Go, go, go!
进入三级戒备状态
Take us to DEFCON 3.
总统先生 我们已开启红色预警
Mr. President, we are Code Red.
防空戒备呢
What's our air defense readiness?
防空戒备已经准备就绪
All our air defenses are ready one.
刚才到底是什么情况
What the hell happened out there?
我能解决
I will fix it.
这话你已经说过了
You said that before.
我本来要发表声明的
I wanted to make a statement.
现在全世界都知道 我们无力保护他们了
Now the whole goddamn world knows we can't protect them.
我能解决
I will fix it.
最好这样
You damn well better.
查尔斯
Charles!
不 不 不
No, no, no...
大家都没事吧
Is everybody okay?
不
No!
小心上方
Behind you.
啊
Ah!
快
Now!
履行你们的使命吧
Do what you were made for.
你们在哪里
Where are you?
啊
Ah!
这交给我 快走
I got this! Go!
上帝啊
Oh, dear God, no.
今天是你的终结之日
So much for being a survivor.
变种人混进来了
One of them is in here.
不 不 不 别杀她
No, no, no! Don't kill it!
我要抓活的
I need it alive.
怎么回事
What the hell has happened?
你们造了这些武器来消灭我们
You built these weapons to destroy us.
为什么
Why?
因为你们畏惧我们的天赋
Because you are afraid of our gifts.
因为我们与众不同
Because we are different.
人类总是恐惧与他们不同的东西
Humanity has always feared that which is different.
我现在告诉你们
Well, I am here to tell you...
告诉这个世界
to tell the world...
你们应该畏惧我们
you are right to fear us.
我们才是未来
We are the future.
我们才是继承这个星球的人
We are the ones who will inherit this earth.
凡是妨碍我们的那些人
And anyone who stands in our way...
都将会面对
will suffer the same fate as these men...
和他们同样的命运
you see before you.
你们原本想要展示你们的力量
Today was meant to be a display of your power.
可我给你们一个小小的提醒
Instead I give you a glimpse...
我的种族能对你们造成毁灭性的打击
of the devastation my race can unleash upon yours.
就把这当作对世界的警告吧
Let this be a warning to the world.
而对我的变种人兄弟姐妹
And to my mutant brothers and sisters out there...
我要说
I say this.
不必躲藏
No more hiding.
不必再受苦
No more suffering.
你们已在羞耻和恐惧的
You have lived in the shadows...
阴影里生活得太久了 出来吧
in shame and fear for too long. Come out.
和我一起
Join me.
团结一心 携手作战
Fight together in a brotherhood of our kind.
崭新的明天
A new tomorrow...
将从今天开始
that starts today.
我们浪费了这么多年
All those years wasted...
你争我斗 查尔斯
fighting each other, Charles.
为了找回那些珍贵的岁月
To have a precious few of them back...
总统先生
让开
Mr. President, sir.
Stand down.
别拦着我
I said, stand down!
你想发表声明
You want to make a statement?
想杀我 没关系
Kill me. Fine.
放过其他人
But spare everyone else.
想当英雄 总统先生
Very heroic, Mr. President...
可你怎么没想过
but you had no intention...
放过我们
of sparing any of us.
我们种族的未来将从现在开始
The future of our species begins now.
你以前可是神枪手
You used to be a better shot.
相信我 现在也是
Trust me, I still am.
从我脑子里出去 查尔斯
Get out of my head, Charles!
瑞雯
Raven.
请不要把我们变成敌人
Please, do not make us the enemy today.
看看周围 我们已经是了
Look around you. We already are.
不全是这样
Not all of us.
到目前为止
All you've done so far...
你是救了这些人的英雄
is save the lives of these men.
你可以让他们看到更好的结局
You can show them a better path.
放倒她 查尔斯
Shut her down, Charles.
从我们认识那天起 我就一直想控制你
I've been trying to control you ever since the day we met...
才让我们变成今天这样
and look where that's got us.
此时此刻 发生的一切
Everything that happens now...
都掌握在你手里
is in your hands.
我对你有信心 瑞雯
I have faith in you, Raven.
他留给你了 查尔斯
He's all yours, Charles.
你把我交给他们 我还不如死了
If you let them have me, I'm as good as dead.
你知道吗
You know that.
我知道
I know.
再见 老朋友
Goodbye, old friend.
再见 埃瑞克
Goodbye, Erik.
你确定要放他们走吗
Are you sure you should let them go?
是的
Yes.
我对他们抱有希望
I have hope for them.
总有一天 汉克 我们会走到一起
There's going to be a time, Hank, when we are all together.
那罗根呢
What about Logan?
The first time
Ever I saw your face
I thought the sun...
巴克敏斯特·富勒在建筑界的优秀案例
Buckminster Fuller is a great example of an architect...
他的观念和乌托邦主义者极为相似
whose ideas were very similar to those of a utopian future.
早上好 罗根 起晚了吧
Good morning, Logan. Late start.
午饭多吃点
Have a good lunch.
干得好
谢谢
Good job.
Thank you.
非常好
Very good job.
暴风女
Storm.
琴
Jean.
嗨 罗根
Hey, Logan.
琴
Jean.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
你在这里
You're here.
那我在哪里
Where else would I be?
喔
Whoa.
悠着点 伙计
Easy, pal.
有些事永远不变
Well, some things never change.
见到你真好 斯科特
It's good to see you, Scott.
嗯哼
Uh-huh.
待会见 琴
See you later, Jean.
教授
Professor.
罗根 没出什么事吧
Logan, is everything all right?
没事
Yeah.
对 我想是的
Yeah, I think it is.
你做到了
You did it.
做到什么
Did what?
罗根 你不是要去上课吗
Logan, don't you have a class to teach?
上课
A class to teach?
历史课
History.
History?
是啊 我是要补习一下
Actually, I could use some help with that.
补习什么
Help with what?
补习从1973年以后所发生的一切
Pretty much everything after 1973.
我知道的历史应该有些不同
I think the history I know is a little different.
欢迎回来
Welcome back.
很高兴见到你 查尔斯
It's good to see you, Charles.
还有大家
It's good to see everyone.
喔
Well...
我那时答应过你的
I had a promise to keep.
我们有好多过去的事情要聊一聊
You and I have a lot of catching up to do.
是啊
Yeah.
你记得最后的事是什么
What's the last thing you remember?
在水里
Drowning.
过去
The past.
一个未知
A new...
多变的世界
and uncertain world.
一个拥有无限可能的世界
A world of endless possibilities.
以及无穷的结局
And infinite outcomes.
怎么了
You kidding me?
什么 他还活着
Oh, he's alive!
无数的选择造就了我们的命运
Countless choices define our fate.
每一个选择 每一个瞬间
Each choice, each moment...
在时间的长河里泛起一道涟漪
a ripple in the river of time.
怎么处置他 史崔克少校
What do you want us to do with him, Major Stryker?
涟漪足够多
Enough ripples...
就能改变水流
and you change the tide.
把他交给我吧
I'll take him from here.
因为未来永远不是定数
For the future is never truly set.